gingermedia.com 2018-03-21

# Ginger Media, Privacy Policy

* * *

### 1\. Privacy Policy  

Ginger Media, as part of providing online services, may ask you to provide us with certain personal information, for example, your name, date of birth, e-mail address etc.  
Ginger Media takes all reasonable steps to protect the privacy of our customers and ensures that the personal information we collect is not ordinarily disclosed to third parties without the customerРІР‚в„ўs consent. Ginger Media has numerous security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of our customerРІР‚в„ўs information. All customer information is password protected and only accessible by authorized members of the Ginger Media staff.  
However, there may be times when Ginger Media may be required to disclose personal information of a customer without his/her express consent when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against the customer.  
While Ginger Media, our associates and affiliates make every effort to protect your personal information and your privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online, that information can be collected and used by people that neither we nor you will know.  
By using this website or our affiliated websites, you signify your assent to our terms and conditions. If you do not agree to be bound by our terms, we politely ask that you do not use this.

* * *
